boardofinnovation.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy policy

                               Privacy policy
1.  Introduction
1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. and
    service users.
1.2 This policy applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to
    the personal data of our website visitors and service users; in other words,
    where we determine the purposes and means of the processing of that
    personal data.
1.3 We use cookies on our website. Insofar as those cookies are not strictly
    necessary for the provision of our website and services, we will ask you to
    consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website.
1.4 In this policy, "we", "us" and "our" refer to Board of Innovation. For more
    information about us, see Section 13.
2.  Credit
2.1 This document was created using a template from SEQ Legal
    (https://seqlegal.com).
3.  How we use your personal data
3.1 In this Section 3 we have set out:
    (a)    the general categories of personal data that we may process;
    (b)    the purposes for which we may process personal data; and
    (c)    the legal bases of the processing.
3.2 We may process data about your use of our website and services ("usage
    data"). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location,
    browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit,
    page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the
    timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage
    data is Google Analytics & Hubspot. This usage data may be processed for the
    purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for
    this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and
    improving our website and services.
3.3 We may process your information included in your personal profile on our
    website ("profile data"). The profile data may include your name, address,
    telephone number, email address, date of birth, relationship status, interests
    and hobbies, educational details and employment details. The profile data
    may be processed for the purposes of enabling and monitoring your use of
    our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our

    legitimate interests OR the performance of a contract between you and us
    and/or taking steps, at you request, to enter into such a contract OR your job
    application to join our team.
3.4 We may process your personal data that are provided in the course of the use
    of our services ("service data"). The service data may be processed [for the
    purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the
    security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases
    and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is consent
    OR our legitimate interests OR the performance of a contract between you
    and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract OR
    your job application to join our team.
3.5 We may process information that you post for publication on our website or
    through our services ("publication data"). The publication data may be
    processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our
    website and services. The legal basis for this processing is consent OR our
    legitimate interests OR the performance of a contract between you and us
    and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract OR your
    job application to join our team.
3.6 We may process information contained in any enquiry you submit to us
    regarding goods and/or services ("enquiry data"). The enquiry data may be
    processed for the purposes of offering, marketing and selling relevant goods
    and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
3.7 We may process information relating to our customer relationships, including
    customer contact information ("customer relationship data"). The
    customer relationship data may include your name, your employer, your job
    title or role, your contact details, and information contained in
    communications between us and you or your employer. The source of the
    customer relationship data is you. The customer relationship data may be
    processed for the purposes of managing our relationships with customers,
    communicating with customers, keeping records of those communications
    and promoting our products and services to customers. The legal basis for
    this processing is consent OR our legitimate interests.
3.8 We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of
    goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website
    ("transaction data"). The transaction data may include your contact details,
    your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be
    processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and
    keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this
    processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or
    taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate
    interests.
3.9 We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of
    subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters ("notification
    data"). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending
    you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this

     processing is consent OR the performance of a contract between you and us
     and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
3.10 We may process information contained in or relating to any communication
     that you send to us ("correspondence data"). The correspondence data
     may include the communication content and metadata associated with the
     communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with
     communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence
     data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and
     record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests,
     namely the proper administration of our website and business and
     communications with users OR your job application to join our team.
3.11 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where
     necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether
     in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The
     legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the
     protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal
     rights of others.
3.12 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where
     necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage,
     managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this
     processing is our legitimate interests, namely [the proper protection of our
     business against risks.
3.13 In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal
     data set out in this Section 3, we may also process any of your personal data
     where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to
     which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital
     interests of another natural person.
3.14 Please do not supply any other person's personal data to us, unless we
     prompt you to do so.
4.   Providing your personal data to others
4.1  We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional
     advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or
     maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional
     advice, or the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in
     court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
4.2  Financial transactions relating to our website and services may be handled by
     our payment services providers (Paypal & Shopify). We will share transaction
     data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the
     purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing
     with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can
     find information about the payment services providers' privacy policies and

    practices at https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy,
    https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full .
4.3 In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section
    4, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for
    compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to
    protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We
    may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for
    the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court
    proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
5.  International transfers of your personal data
5.1 The hosting facilities for our website are situated in Belgium via Combell.com.
6.  Retaining and deleting personal data
6.1 This Section 6 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are
    designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation
    to the retention and deletion of personal data.
6.2 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept
    for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
6.3 We will retain your personal data as follows:
    Newsletter subscriptions:
    (a)    Name, Surname, email address, job title will be retained until you
           unsubscribe.
    Job applications
    (a)    Name, Surname, email address, job title & other personal info you will
           disclose during the recruitments process will be retained for a maximum
           period of 5 years. If after applying for a job, you do not want to be kept
           in our database, your data will be removed maximum 3 months after
           applying.
6.4 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 6, we may retain your
    personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal
    obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests
    or the vital interests of another natural person.
7.  Amendments
7.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on
    our website.

7.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any
    changes to this policy.
8.  Your rights
8.1 In this Section 8, we have summarised the rights that you have under data
    protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have
    been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant
    laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of
    these rights.
8.2 Your principal rights under data protection law are:
    (a)    the right to access;
    (b)    the right to rectification;
    (c)    the right to erasure;
    (d)    the right to restrict processing;
    (e)    the right to object to processing;
    (f)    the right to data portability;
    (g)    the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
    (h)    the right to withdraw consent.
8.3 You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your
    personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with
    certain additional information. That additional information includes details of
    the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned
    and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of
    others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data.
    The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be
    subject to a reasonable fee.
8.4 You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified
    and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any
    incomplete personal data about you completed.
8.5 In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal
    data without undue delay. Those circumstances include:[the personal data
    are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were
    collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based
    processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable
    data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the
    personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions
    of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is
    necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information;

     for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or
     defence of legal claims.
8.6  In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your
     personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the
     personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer
     need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require
     personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and
     you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection.
     Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store
     your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your
     consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the
     protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of
     important public interest.
8.7  You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on
     grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the
     legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the
     performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of
     any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests
     pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will
     cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate
     compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your
     interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment,
     exercise or defence of legal claims.
8.8  You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct
     marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you
     make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this
     purpose.
8.9  You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for
     scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds
     relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the
     performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.
8.10 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:
     (a)    consent; or
     (b)    that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to
            which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to
            entering into a contract,
     and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right
     to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and
     machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would
     adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.
8.11 If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes
     data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a
     supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the

     EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place
     of the alleged infringement.
8.12 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal
     information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any
     time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the
     withdrawal.
8.13 You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by
     written notice to us OR by contacting us via privacy@boardofinnovation.com
     in addition to the other methods specified in this Section 8].
9.   About cookies
9.1  A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that
     is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The
     identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a
     page from the server.
9.2  Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent
     cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set
     expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session
     cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the
     web browser is closed.
9.3  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a
     user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the
     information stored in and obtained from cookies.
10.  Cookies that we use
10.1 We use cookies for the following purposes:
     (a)    authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our
            website and as you navigate our website.
     (b)    analysis - we use cookies to help us to analyse the use and
            performance of our website and services
     (c)    cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to
            the use of cookies more generally.
11.  Cookies used by our service providers
11.1 Our service providers use cookies and those cookies maybe stored on your
     computer when you visit our website.
11.2 We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics
     gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information
     gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our
     website. Google's privacy policy is available at:
     https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

11.3 We use Hubspot to track the website usage of our website. Hubspot’s privacy
     policy is available at: https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy
12.  Managing cookies
12.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies.
     The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to
     version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and
     deleting cookies via these links:
     (a)   https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);
     (b)   https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-
           website-preferences (Firefox);
     (c)   http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);
     (d)   https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-
           explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);
     (e)   https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and
     (f)   https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-
           privacy (Edge).
12.2 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many
     websites.
12.3 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our
     website.
13.  Our details
13.1 This website is owned and operated by Board of Innovation bvba.
13.2 We are registered in Belgium under registration number BE0818009314, and
     our registered office is at Karel Oomsstraat 1 box 65, 2018 Antwerpen
     Belgium.
13.3 Our principal place of business is at Karel Oomsstraat 1 box 65, 2018
     Antwerpen Belgium.
13.4 You can contact us:
     (a)   by post, to the postal address given above;
     (b)   using our website contact form: www.boardofinnovation.com/contact
     (c)   by email: privacy@boardofinnovation.com.
14.  Data protection officer
14.1 Our data protection officer's contact details are: Nick De Mey
     nick@boardofinnovation.com.
